http://www.jayandsilentbobstrikeback.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
You Are Here
At Jayandsilentbobstrikeback.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Jayandsilentbobstrikeback.com and how it is used.
Log Files
Like many other Web sites, Jayandsilentbobstrikeback.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file (often including a unique identifier), that is sent to a user’s browser from a website’s computers and stored on a user’s computer’s hard drive or on a tablet or mobile device (collectively, “Computer”). A Cookie stores a small amount of data on your Computer about your visit to the Site.
We may also use “web beacons” (also known as “clear GIFs” or “pixel tags”) or similar technologies on our Site to enable us to know whether you have visited a web page or received a message. A web beacon is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a web page which is retrieved from a remote website on the internet enabling the verification of an individual’s viewing or receipt of a web page or message. A web beacon helps us to understand whether you came to our website from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website, measure successes of email marketing campaigns and improve our website performance.
We place and access Cookies on your Computer; these Cookies are known as “first-party Cookies.” Cookies may also be placed and accessed by some of our third-party vendors, which are known as “third-party Cookies” and are described below. Some Cookies are “session Cookies,” which means that they are temporary Cookies that are only stored on your device while you are visiting our Site. Other Cookies are “persistent Cookies,” which means that they are stored on your device for a period of time after you leave our Site.
You can choose whether to accept Cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you disable this function (or keep this function disabled, as set by default by certain browsers), your experience on the Site may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.
Information about the procedure to follow in order to enable or disable Cookies can be found at:
Chrome
Safari
Safari Mobile (iPhones & iPads)
Firefox
Microsoft Edge
WordPress Cookies
WordPress uses cookies, or tiny pieces of information stored on your computer, to verify who you are. There are cookies for logged in users and for commenters – read more here.
Analytics Cookies
Google Analytics collect information about your use of the Site, and enable us to improve the way it works. For example, Google Analytics show us which are the most frequently visited pages on the Site, help us record any difficulties you have with the Site, and show us whether our advertising is effective or not.
We use Google Analytics, which collects anonymous data for us to better serve you with both better website design and content.
What Google Analytics features do we use? Please see the feature list for Google Analytics at http://www.google.com/analytics/features.What do we do with your data? All tracking information is used to help better design our content and web design to meet the needs of the customer and enhance the Service. All of our activity meets Google Analytics Terms of Service which can be found here. http://www.google.com/analytics/terms.Opt out of Google Analytics: You can opt out of the anonymous data collected from Google Analytics by disabling cookies in your web browser for the Services. This will only block Google Analytics Data for us, and will not affect other websites. You can also opt out of all Google Analytics Tracking Data on the web by installing a browser plugin provided by Google. This can be found here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. The anonymous statistics we gather may be shared with a third party vendor to assist us with analyzing data, creating ads and web design. For more information about how Google uses data, visit http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners.
Advertising Cookies
Advertising Cookies are set to display targeted promotions or advertisements based upon your interests on the Site or to manage our advertising. These Cookies collect information about your activities on this Site and other websites to provide you targeted advertising.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Jayandsilentbobstrikeback.com.Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Jayandsilentbobstrikeback.com and other sites on the Internet.Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL’s –Google Adsense: Privacy Policy Google
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Jayandsilentbobstrikeback.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
Jayandsilentbobstrikeback.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Jayandsilentbobstrikeback.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
Embedded content
Articles on this site may include embedded YouTube content. Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. Check out the YouTube Privacy Policy here.
Links to Other Sites
Jayandsilentbobstrikeback.com has links to partners, sources and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.
Mailing list or newsletter
By registering on the mailing list or for the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning this Application. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to this Application.
FeedBurner (Google Inc.)
FeedBurner is an email address management and message sending service provided by Google Inc.
Personal Data collected: email address.
Place of processing: US – Privacy Policy
Social Media Cookies
Social media Cookies are used to enable you to share pages and content you find interesting on our Site through third-party social networking and other websites. These Cookies may also be used for advertising purposes.
Facebook Like&Share button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)The Facebook Like&Share button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.Place of processing: US – Privacy Policy
Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets (Pinterest)The Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Pinterest platform provided by Pinterest Inc.Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.Place of processing: US – Privacy Policy
Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter, Inc.)
The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter, Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: US – Privacy Policy
Contact forms
A “contact us” form is a form where you can contact the owner of the website by typing in your contact information, name, email address and your message. Jayandsilentbobstrikeback.com keep contact form submissions for a certain period only for customer service purposes.
Restriction of Liability
Jayandsilentbobstrikeback.com makes no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this website and expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this website.
No warranty of any kind, implied, expressed or statutory, including but not limited to the warranties of non-infringement of third party rights, title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and freedom from computer virus, is given with respect to the contents of this website or its hyperlinks to other Internet resources.
Reference in this website to any specific commercial products, processes, or services, or the use of any trade, firm or corporation name is for the information and convenience of the public, and does not constitute endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by Jayandsilentbobstrikeback.com
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and if we do we’ll post any changes on this page. If you continue to use the Services after those changes are in effect, you agree to the revised Privacy Policy. If the changes are significant, we may provide more prominent notice or get your consent as required by law.
Contacting Us
If you have any requests concerning your personal information or other inquiries regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via “Contact Us” page.
Search for:
Golf Putting
Outdoor Putting Green Kits – Tips for Finding the Best Kit
An Overview On All Kinds Of Golf Putting Aids Available To A Golfer For Putting
Know Golf Kick Back Putting Aids Better
Golf Putting Cups, Its Merits And Use For Golfers In Putting
New Posts
Golf Cars Recommendation – Checking out the Best Rated Models
EZ Go Golf Carts – Tips on Finding a Reasonably Priced Model
Harley Davidson Golf Cart for Sale – How to Find a Quality Model
Swing Better for Your Longer Golf Drives
Keep Your Trolley Rolling With The Right Golf Trolley Battery
